Alejandro Ohrnialian Bengolea



aob@live.com.ar



linkedin.com/in/a-ob



https://certificates.soyhenry.com/new-cert? id=45638f7141708eab6aec3f23f2e751df511dd4b3b102e443feb2

Summary

https://github.com/AOB1992 I am a FullStack Developer with a huge entrepreneur background. I have experience in the finance and mobility industries. I have a huge experience in sales and in management. I know what the client needs and I know that it needs it fast. That is why I can deliver solutions that suits the client. And I make that quick.

Experience



Full-stack Developer

Profesional independiente Mar 2023 - Present (3 months)



CEO & Owner

Dynamic Transport S.R.L Mar 2020 - Mar 2022 (2 years 1 month)



CEO & Owner

Jun 2016 - May 2019 (3 years)



Account executive

AIG

Dec 2015 - Feb 2016 (3 months) Insurance sales and counseling



Junior Account Executive

Galicia Seguros (Grupo Financiero Galicia, Banco Galicia)

Jun 2012 - Jan 2013 (8 months)

House Insurance sales.

Education



::- Henry

Fullstack Developer

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

GIT ADVANCED JS DATA STRUCTURE ALGORITMS DOM ADVANCED CSS ES6 AJAX REACT REDUX NODEJS PROMISES WEB SERVER EXPRESS TESTING SQL ORM SEQUELIZE

University of Buenos Aires

Economy

2012 - 2018

Colegio Granaderos

High School Diploma in Economics 2011 - 2011

Santo Tomás de Aquino

High School Diplma 2005 - 2010

Licenses & Certifications

Cambridge ESOL Level 1 Certificate in ESOL International - University of Cambridge

0026078110

English Certificate - EF International Language Campuses efset.org/cert/DYjvyB

Skills

Inglés bilingüe • Análisis financiero • Eficacia de ventas • Mercado de divisas • Análisis de acciones cotizadas • Derivados sobre acciones • Bonos • Trabajo en equipo • Liderazgo de equipos • Inglés

Honors & Awards

November best salesman - Galicia Seguros

Nov 2012

Recognition for being the best seller of the month of November

■ December best salesman - Galicia Seguros

Dec 2012

Recognition for being the best seller of the month of December